

Pejman Kiamehr

Junior Front-End Developer with React

Summary

Experienced React Developer More than 1 year of experience in website development and also organizational panels with React. Familiarity with Restfull api and experience of cooperation with backend developer, proficient in Responsive design and familiarity with SEO. I am currently looking for an opportunity to work with a team of several front-end developers.

Contact Information

Phone 0915 550 3369

Email pejman.kiamehr@gmail.com

Work samples

MyWebsite www.pejmankiamehr.ir

Github https://github.com/pkiamehr

Technical Skills

 $React Js \quad context API, restfull Api, react Bootstrap, Material UI, Ant Desing, Responsive Design, react Hooks, axios and the property of th$

fundamentals HTML, CSS, JavaScript, E6, Media-Query, Bootstrap, JQuery, Less

VC Git, Github, Gitlab

Others postman, figma, trello, Scrum, Latex

Professional Experiences

2023–2024 Customer affairs expert, mashhad.

Iran server (Green Web)

2021–2022 Front end developer, Mashhad.

Eight Team

2018–2020 **Customer affairs expert**, *Tehran*.

Romak Holding (Snapp Team)

2016-2017 Website admin, Mashhad.

Yekta Mana Company

2015–2016 Content production specialist, Mashhad.

Yekta Mana Company

Education

2019–2020 **Tehran Institute of Technology**, *Tehran*.

Web Package Design: web1,web2,web3

2009-2013 Islamic Azad University, Mashhad.

BSc. of Mechanical Engineering

Soft skills

- 1. Embraces teamwork, Team-oriented personality
- 2. Excellent written and verbal communication skills
- 3. Excellent presentation and negotiation skills